[
	{
		"question": "What do devices need to communicate?",
		"options": [
			"A physical address",
			"All of them",
			"Network address",
			"Set of protocols"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is packet sniffing?",
		"options": [
			"The attacker blocks the communication between two or multiple nodes",
			"The attacker impersonates another by changing the packet's transmitter address",
			"The attackers capture and analyze the communication among other nodes"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What does an attacker need to sniff packets?",
		"options": [
			"A powerful device",
			"To be able to manipulate packets",
			"To be connected to the communication medium of the victim"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Choose the option(s) that hold true for the NIC card",
		"options": [
			"It is associated with an IP address",
			"It is a physical and logical interface for communications",
			"It communicates with the kernel to pass packets to the user interface",
			"It's sole purpose is spoofing"
		],
		"correctAnswer": [1, 2],
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The promiscuous mode is needed to:",
		"options": [
			"Discard packets not intended to the receiver NIC",
			"Pass to the kernel packets with MAC address different from the NIC one",
			"Capture packets in a wireless network",
			"Change the IP address of the sender of the current packet"
		],
		"correctAnswer": [1],
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is spoofing?",
		"options": [
			"The process where all packets in the network are captured by the attacker",
			"The process by which some critical information in the packet is forged",
			"The process where the MAC address of the sender is changed",
			"The process where the IP address of the sender is changed"
		],
		"correctAnswer": [1],
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a smurf attack?",
		"options": [
			"A spoofing attack in TCP to overload a victim",
			"A spoofing attack in ICMP to overload the whole network",
			"A spoofing attack in ICMP to overload a victim"
		],
		"correctAnswer": [2],
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Buffer overflow attacks result from careless programming in applications.",
		"options": [
			"True",
			"False"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 0,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The only consequence of a buffer overflow attack is the possible corruption of data used by the program.",
		"options": [
			"True",
			"False"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What happens when a buffer is overflowed?",
		"options": [
			"Whatever is in the memory space that comes after the buffer is overwritten",
			"The memory space that comes after the buffer holds the extra data as well as keeping the data that it contained before"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 0,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "To exploit any type of buffer overflow the attacker needs to understand how that buffer will be stored in the process's memory.",
		"options": [
			"False",
			"True"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The JAVA programming language is extremely vulnerable to buffer overflows.",
		"options": [
			"True",
			"False"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What does a typical C program usually use stacks for?",
		"options": [
			"Permanent storage of variables",
			"For preventing buffer overflows",
			"Temporary storage of variables"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "If you declare an array as A[100] in C and you try to write data to A[555], what will happen?",
		"options": [
			"Nothing",
			"The C compiler will give you an error and won't compile",
			"Whatever is at A[555] will be overwritten"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2,
		"verified": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What can be overwritten by a buffer overflow that causes a security problem?",
		"options": [
			"The original binary code of the program",
			"Permanent data saved on the computer",
			"Any kind of pointer"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2,
		"verified": 1
	}
]
